lifeisbeautiful.com 2019-05-19

# Privacy Policy - LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL Music & Art Festival

#### 1\. THIS PRIVACY POLICY

The Web Site located at [www.lifeisbeautiful.com](http://www.lifeisbeautiful.com/) (the “Web Site”) is operated by LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL, LLC (hereinafter referred to as “LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL”). This privacy policy describes LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL’s current policies and practices with regard to personal data collected by LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL through the Web Site. This privacy policy is independent from LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL’s offline personal data collection practices. This privacy policy forms part of the LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL Terms and Conditions

#### 2\. NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES TO THIS POLICY

LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL is continually improving and adding new functionality and features to its Web Site and improving and adding to our existing products, services, and programs. Because of these ongoing changes, changes in the law, and the changing nature of technology, LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL’s data practices will change from time to time. If and when our data practices change, LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL will post the changes on the Web Site to notify you of the changes. We encourage you to check this page frequently. This policy was last updated on December 31, 2016.

#### 3\. PERSONAL DATA COLLECTED

LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL collects information and data when you use the Web Site. Such information includes Personal Information, Contact Data, Message Data, and Traffic Data (collectively “Customer Information”). “Personal Information” includes your name, address, email address, passwords, home and business address, phone number(s), and other information that may not be publicly available. “Contact Data” includes information developed by you that may be provided to LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL to enhance your use of LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL products and services. “Message Data” includes any messages sent or received through the Web Site, information and data about those messages, your account activity, and your log-in, log-out times. “Traffic Data” includes data about the nature of your usage of the Web Site and products and services and can include: IP addresses, domain servers, referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, clickstream data, type of computer or mobile phone, type of web browser, one or more cookies that identify your browser, and telecommunications carrier information.

In connection with your use of the Web Site, LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL may collect: the domain name and/or email address of Web Site visitors; the email address of users who communicate with LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL via the Web Site or via email; information as to what pages within the Web Site users access, and for how long the users access or visit such page; information volunteered by the user, such as through registration on the Web Site, purchases made through the Web Site, email update requests, and general requests for information; and information about transactions with LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL, and third-parties with whom LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL affiliates for ticketing, merchandising, and other commercial purposes.

LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL honors Do Not Track (“DNT”) signals and does not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a DNT browser mechanism is in place.

LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL CANNOT GUARANTEE THE SECURITY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION ACCESSIBLE ON OR TRANSMITTED VIA THE INTERNET.

#### 4\. USE OF CUSTOMER INFORMATION

When you register on the Web Site, or make a purchase transaction on the Web Site or through a LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL ticketing or merchandising partner, your personal information will not be sold, shared, rented or distributed to others, including sponsors, affiliates, and partners (the “Affiliated Parties”). However, there may be some other, limited circumstances in which LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL may be required to share or transfer Personal Information in our databases, for example, to comply with a legal requirement, for the administration of justice, to protect your vital interests, or in the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution, or similar event. LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL restricts access to nonpublic Personal Information to those employees and agents who need such information. LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL maintains physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to guard your nonpublic personal information.

LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL uses Customer Information to enhance your use of LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL services by processing information collected for purposes including, but not limited to: providing information to users about LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL products and services; formatting and displaying elements of Contact Data and Message Data to you and those with whom you exchange messages; delivering advertisements and related links; and storing messages.

LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL may engage third-parties to perform functions on its behalf, including: sending of newsletters, postal mail, and email; analyzing and processing data; payment processing; and providing customer service. LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL requires that these parties agree to use Personal Information in compliance with this privacy policy, and in accordance with any other appropriate confidentiality and security procedures. These parties may have access to Customer Information needed to perform their functions, but LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL will not authorize them to use it for purposes that do not conform to this privacy policy. For more information on third-parties, see Section 8 – Third-Parties below.

If LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL intends to use Personal Information for purposes other than those described in this privacy policy, LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL will offer you the opportunity to opt out of such use of your Personal Information for those other purposes. For more information on how to opt out, see Section 7 – Opt In/Opt Out, below.

#### 5\. ANONYMOUS DATA COLLECTED

In addition to the information you provide when you use [www.lifeisbeautiful.com](http://www.lifeisbeautiful.com/), LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL uses technology to collect anonymous information about the use of our Web Site. For example, we use technology to track how many visitors access our Web Site, the date and time of their visit, the length of their stay, and which pages they view. We also use technology to determine which web browsers our visitors use and the address from which they accessed our sites (for example, if they connected to the Web Site by clicking on a banner ad).

This technology does not identify you personally. It simply enables us to compile statistics about our visitors and their use of the Web Site. LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL and our Affiliates use this anonymous data and share it with third-parties to improve the content and functionality of our Web Site, to better understand our customers and markets, and to improve our products and services.

#### 6\. COOKIES

A cookie is a small piece of information that is sent to your browser and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies do not damage your computer, and they cannot be used to discover the identity of a user. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie. This enables you to decide if you want to accept it or not, and whether you are required to accept the cookie to view certain content. LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL may use cookies to “persist” a user session — that is, to maintain connection with a user as he or she moves through an application or series of web pages. The purpose of cookies in this context is to remember user inputs. Personalization features also use cookies to identify groups of users and deliver appropriate content and services.

#### 7\. OPT IN/OPT OUT

As noted in Use of Customer Information above, LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL will not provide your nonpublic Personal Information to Affiliated Parties unless you have opted in to receive emails from the Affiliated Parties. If, at any time, you desire that LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL cease providing your nonpublic Personal Information to Affiliated Parties, you may opt out of those disclosures by directing us not to make those disclosures (other than disclosures permitted by law). If you receive communications from us that you do not want to receive, you may opt out of receiving those communications by clicking the unsubscribe link in the email or emailing us at info@lifeisbeautiful.com. Occasionally it is necessary to send out a service-related announcement. Generally, users may not opt out of these communications. These communications are not promotional in nature.

#### 8\. THIRD-PARTIES

LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL may share aggregate information about our users with advertisers, business partners, sponsors, and other third-parties, though such summary information will not identify any specifics related to you. We may use the Personal Information you provide to administer Web Site usage and monitor traffic-levels, and to contact you regarding improvements we can make to our Web Site and our services, if necessary. LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL may engage third-parties to perform functions on its behalf, such as sending newsletters, postal mail and e-mail, analyzing and processing data, payment processing, and providing customer service. LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL requires that these parties agree to use Personal Information in compliance with this privacy policy, and in accordance with any other appropriate confidentiality and security procedures. These parties may have access to Customer Information needed to perform their functions, but LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL will not authorize them to use it for purposes that do not conform to this privacy policy. LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL will apply the Opt In/Opt Out policies discussed above in the event we propose to disclose your information to a third-party.

LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL does not disclose personal information to third-parties, except when one or more of the following conditions is true:

  1. LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL has the individual’s permission to make the disclosure;
  2. The disclosure is permitted by law or mandatory professional standards;
  3. The disclosure is reasonably related to the sale or other disposition of all or part of LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL’s business or assets or in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, or other corporate reorganization;
  4. The personal information to be disclosed is publicly available;
  5. The party to whom the disclosure is made controls, is controlled by, or is under common control with LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL;
  6. The disclosure is reasonably necessary for the establishment or maintenance of legal claims;
  7. The disclosure is to persons or entities for whom LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL is providing or receiving services, provided the disclosure is consistent with the purpose for which the personal information was obtained;
  8. LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL may share with third-parties certain aggregated, non-personal information and Traffic Data, but such information will not identify you individually;
  9. LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL may share Customer Information when legally required to do so or at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation; or
  10. LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL may share your Customer Information with a third-party if you have consented to receive information from that third-party through registration from a co-branded version of the LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL service operated with a third-party or through a communication or promotional program of a third-party that is enabled by the LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL Service. Such third-parties will handle, store, retain, and access such user information in accordance with the terms and conditions of their agreements with you, if any, as well as their own privacy policies. It is your responsibility to carefully review such agreements and privacy policies. You acknowledge that LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL shall have no liability to you for sharing of such information to such third-parties and LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL disclaims any and all liability relating thereto.

#### 9\. PUBLIC FORUMS

Lifeisbeautiful.com may make chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups (collectively, “Public Areas”) available to its users. Please remember that any information that is posted to and/or disclosed in these Public Areas becomes public information, and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. By posting in the Public Areas you grant LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL a license to use the materials you post to the Web Site or any related service. By posting, downloading, displaying, performing, transmitting, or otherwise distributing information or other content (“User Content”) to the Web Site or related service, you are granting LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL, its Affiliates, officers, directors, employees, consultants, agents, and representatives a license to use User Content in connection with the operation of the Web Site, including without limitation: a right to copy, distribute, transmit, publicly display, publicly perform, reproduce, edit, translate, and reformat User Content. You will not be compensated for any User Content. You agree that LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL may publish or otherwise disclose your name in connection with your User Content. By posting User Content on the Web Site or any related service, you warrant and represent that you own the rights to the User Content or are otherwise authorized to post, distribute, display, perform, transmit, or otherwise distribute such User Content.

#### 10\. CHILDREN

The LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL Web Site is not directed at children under the age of thirteen. LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL does not knowingly collect personal data from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under thirteen, please do not transmit any personal data. If you have reason to believe that a child has provided personal data to LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL, please contact us at [info@lifeisbeautiful.com](mailto:info@lifeisbeautiful.com), and we will try to delete that information from our databases.

#### 11\. LINK TO OTHER SITES

This privacy policy applies only to LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL’s Web Site at [www.lifeisbeautiful.com](http://www.lifeisbeautiful.com/) and LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL and our Affiliates operate other websites for different purposes and in different countries where different laws may apply. If you visit the LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL Web Site, including [www.lifeisbeautiful.com](http://www.lifeisbeautiful.com/), please take a moment to review the privacy policy posted on that site to learn what personal data may be collected through that website and how it is processed.

The LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL Web Site contains hyperlinks to websites that are not operated by LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL or our Affiliates. These hyperlinks are provided for your reference and convenience only and do not imply any endorsement of the activities of these third-party websites or any association with their operators. LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL does not control these websites, and is not responsible for their data practices. We urge you to review the privacy policy posted on any website you visit before using the website or providing any personal data about yourself.

#### 12\. CONSENT TO BE CONTACTED

By submitting the contact form, I agree by electronic signature to: (1) be contacted about LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL by SMS text at my mobile phone number and by email (consent to be contacted is not a condition to purchase services); and (2) the Privacy Policy and Terms of Use.

#### 13\. GOVERNING LAW

This privacy policy forms part of our Web Site Terms and Conditions and as such shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Nevada.

#### 14\. QUESTIONS ABOUT OUR PRIVACY POLICY

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or concerns about the way LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL processes your personal data, please contact us at [info@lifeisbeautiful.com](mailto:info@lifeisbeautiful.com).

You and Life is Beautiful, LLC agree that we will resolve any disputes between us through binding and final arbitration instead of through court proceedings. All controversies, claims, counterclaims, or other disputes arising between you and Life is Beautiful, LLC relating to the Site, Contest Rules, and Terms of Use (each a “Claim”) shall be submitted for binding arbitration in accordance with the Rules of the American Arbitration Association (“AAA Rules”). The arbitration will be heard and determined by a single arbitrator. The arbitrator’s decision in any such arbitration will be final and binding upon the parties and may be enforced in any court of competent jurisdiction. The parties agree that the arbitration will be kept confidential and that the existence of the proceeding and any element of it (including, without limitation, any pleadings, briefs, documents, or other evidence submitted or exchanged and any testimony or other oral submissions and awards) will not be disclosed beyond the arbitration proceedings, except as may lawfully be required in judicial proceedings relating to the arbitration or by applicable disclosure rules and regulations of securities regulatory authorities or other governmental agencies.

If you demonstrate that the costs of arbitration will be prohibitive as compared to the costs of litigation, Life is Beautiful, LLC will pay as much of the administrative costs and arbitrator’s fees required for the arbitration as the arbitrator deems necessary to prevent the cost of the arbitration from being prohibitive. In the final award, the arbitrator may apportion the costs of arbitration and the compensation of the arbitrator among the parties in such amounts as the arbitrator deems appropriate.

This arbitration agreement does not preclude you from seeking action by federal, state, or local government agencies. You and Life is Beautiful, LLC also have the right to bring qualifying claims in small claims court. In addition, you and Life is Beautiful, LLC retain the right to apply to any court of competent jurisdiction for provisional relief, including pre-arbitral attachments or preliminary injunctions, and any such request shall not be deemed incompatible with these Terms of Use, nor a waiver of the right to have disputes submitted to arbitration as provided herein.

Neither you nor Life is Beautiful, LLC may act as a class representative or private attorney general, nor participate as a member of a class of claimants, with respect to any Claim. Claims may not be arbitrated on a class or representative basis. The arbitrator can decide only your and/or Life is Beautiful, LLC’s individual Claims. The arbitrator may not consolidate or join the claims of other persons or parties who may be similarly situated. This Section will survive the termination of your relationship with Life is Beautiful, LLC.

THIS SECTION LIMITS CERTAIN RIGHTS, INCLUDING THE RIGHT TO MAINTAIN A COURT ACTION, THE RIGHT TO PARTICIPATE IN ANY FORM OF CLASS OR REPRESENTATIVE CLAIM, THE RIGHT TO ENGAGE IN DISCOVERY EXCEPT AS PROVIDED IN AAA RULES, AND THE RIGHT TO CERTAIN REMEDIES AND FORMS OF RELIEF. OTHER RIGHTS THAT YOU OR LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL, LLC WOULD HAVE IN COURT ALSO MAY NOT BE AVAILABLE IN ARBITRATION.
